innovid.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Innovid

Innovid, Inc., having its principal office and place of business at 30 Irving Place, 12th Floor, New York, NY 10003, together with its affiliates, Innovid EU Ltd., Innovid Media Ltd, and Innovid AU PTY Ltd. (“Innovid”) has a strong commitment to protect the data privacy of visitors and users. Our Privacy Notice describes how information is collected and utilised by Innovid. This Privacy Notice (the “Policy”) applies to visitors to the website located at _[Innovid.com](http://www.innovid.com/)_  (the “Innovid Website”), and to Innovid’s online interactive video advertising services provided to various advertisers, agencies, publishers and other business across various third party websites and online media (the “Services”). Please contact us with any questions or concerns at _[privacy@innovid.com](mailto:privacy@innovid.com)_.

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy is paramount to us.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it.  By accessing and using the Innovid Website and using our Services you agree to us processing your information in accordance with this Policy.

The Innovid Website may link to, and the Services may appear on, third party websites and online media. Innovid does not control and is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, and this Policy does not cover collection or use of information by third parties on such properties. Visitors to or users of such third party websites or other media should consult the privacy policies of such properties to learn about such third parties’ privacy practices.

With respect to data governed by the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (“GDPR”), Innovid processes personal data. With respect to data governed by GDPR, and for the benefit of Data Subjects, we have added clarifications to this privacy policy for clarity and transparency.

**Quick Guide to Content**

  1. Innovid Website 
  2. Cookies
  3. Innovid’s Services
  4. Cross-Device Tracking
  5. Industry Self-Regulation
  6. Opt-Out of Interest-Based Advertising
  7. Data Retention
  8. Legal and Regulatory Compliance
  9. Third Party Service Providers
  10. Business Transfers
  11. Newsletter Subscriptions
  12. Aggregate Information
  13. Communication
  14. Data and Information Security
  15. Children’s Privacy
  16. International Data Transfers
  17. EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield
  18. Enforcement Complaints
  19. Contact

#### Innovid Website

Innovid may collect personal data, including IP addresses, cookie information, device ID and/or advertising ID, from visitors to the Innovid Website. This information may be used to monitor usage of the Innovid Website, conduct administration and troubleshooting, and assist in improvements to Innovid Website. Innovid may customize the content the visitor receives in future visits to the Innovid Website based on such visitor’s preferences and activities as determined based upon such data.

**Registration Data and Account Data**

If you register to use the Innovid Website as a customer of the Services (e.g., as an agency, advertiser or publisher customer), Innovid may request and store personal data you provide, such as your name, email address, company name, username, telephone number and address (collectively, “Registration Data”). Following your registration, you may use the Innovid Website to set up your account, view reports and/or manage or view advertising campaigns. Innovid may collect information about the manner of your use of the Innovid Website, including session length, IP Address, time of usage, viewed pages and files, and other information regarding your use of the Innovid Website (collectively with Registration Data, the “Account Data”). Innovid may use and retain Account Data in order to provide the Services to you, manage and maintain the account, conduct internal analysis, perform billing, invoicing and payment functions in connection with your account, send Services-related information, alerts and promotional messages to you, and maintain and improve the performance of the Innovid Website and Services.

Website user data may be combined with a visitor’s Account Data once the visitor has registered for or subsequently logged into the Innovid Website. The combined data is used to provide, monitor and assist in improvements to the Services and the Innovid Website, and to customize content displayed to you on the Innovid Website. Website user data, Account Data, Registration Data, and combined data collected from the Innovid Website is not sold or rented to third parties. In addition, such information is not shared with third parties except in the case of third party service providers, legal processes and aggregate information, as noted below.

**Google Analytics**

Innovid uses Google Analytics, a service provided by Google, to help analyze how users use the Innovid website and user interface. Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on a user’s computer or device, to track the user’s activity (including information such as the user’s flow, location by country, language, browser and OS, ISP and devices) on the Innovid website and user interface. We use this service with a view to analyzing usage across devices and offering improvements for all users. To learn more about Google Analytics, please click _[here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245)_. To opt-out of this feature by installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, please click _[here.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)_

**Intercom**

For customer management purposes, we provide a limited amount of information about users of the Innovid website and user interface (such as the user’s email address and sign-up date) to Intercom, Inc., 98 Battery Street, Suite 402, San Francisco, CA 94111 USA (“Intercom”). We utilize Intercom for additional data analysis, e.g. retrieving a user’s sign-up date or activity when providing customer support. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product. To help us understand our user base, Intercom collects publicly available information, such as a user’s company, job title, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit _[http://docs.intercom.io/privacy](https://docs.intercom.io/pricing-privacy-and-terms/intercom-inc-privacy-policy)_. Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use which can be found at <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms>. If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please contact us directly.

#### Cookies

Innovid may collect the data, including personal data, using cookies, which are small text files stored on the visitor’s computer. Visitors can set their browser to reject cookies altogether, to reject Innovid’s cookies in particular, or to delete cookies. For our EU based website visitors, we may also put in place a Cookie Control Tool on our site. Visitors to third party websites, mobile websites, mobile applications, CTVs and other online media that utilize Innovid’s services may opt-out of interest-based advertising from Innovid; please refer to the Section entitled “Opt-Out of Interest-Based Advertising” below.  

#### Innovid’s Services

Innovid partners with numerous companies to provide and measure online advertisements to visitors of third party websites, mobile websites, mobile applications and other online media. Online media also includes televisions with third party connected applications, smart televisions and/or digital media streaming devices (together, “ **CTVs** “). Visitors to third party websites, mobile websites, mobile applications, CTVs and other online media are referred to as **“End Users”**.

As an End User browses the Internet or uses a CTV, he or she may visit web pages, mobile applications, CTV channels or applications, or other online media that make use of the Services. When this happens, an End User’s browser, device, or CTV may request advertisements from Innovid’s system, and Innovid may collect data about this interaction, as well as about any further interaction by such End User with the advertisements provided by the Services and the pages or media on which such Services are utilized, such as impressions, clicks, mouse movements, viewing duration, IP address, date and time of interaction, information about the general geographical location from which an End User is viewing an advertisement, device type, and other Non-PII made available by the browser or device. In addition, in the event that the data being collected is from a mobile device, Innovid may also collect the mobile advertising ID of the device (e.g. IDFA and Google AdID), and in the event that the data being collected is from a CTV, Innovid may also collect the advertising identifiers made available by the CTV. On occasion, Innovid may also receive from third parties personal data that enables advertisement optimization, independent of or in combination with the data collected by Innovid, such as audience interest segments and product categories.

The data collected by Innovid and/or received from third parties may be shared and used to provide information and reports to advertisers, agencies and publishers who participate in the Services, to schedule, deliver and optimize advertisements, to limit the number of times a specific advertisement is presented to the same browser or device (frequency capping), to detect and eliminate fraudulent activity, to administer and enhance the Services and perform internal analysis, and to help Innovid display, optimize, target and/or customize advertisements to the interests or preferences of End Users. Innovid may use certain general health-related segments received from third parties in delivering advertisements based on inferred End User interest in such topics, such as general health, wellness, common ailments and illnesses, beauty and fitness. Such health-related segments do not include sensitive health information (such as an End User having a certain medical condition like heart disease or arthritis).

From time to time, advertisements served by Innovid may contain functionality that enables an End User to enter personal data into such advertisements or into the landing page to which such advertisements are linked, in order to allow the End User to sign-up for or receive information regarding an advertiser or publisher’s product, service, program or other offer. In the event that an End User elects to provide personal data under such circumstances, Innovid may store such information and may share it with the advertiser, agency or publisher on behalf of whom the advertisement was served, and/or with such entity’s service provider. Innovid may use such information to fulfill or aid in the fulfillment of the End User’s request and/or to auto-populate future requests by the End User’s device. In cases where the advertisement contains functionality enabling Innovid to store personal data, the End User will have the option to opt-out of the storage of such information by indicating its preference in the appropriate checkbox shown in the advertisement, or by clicking through to the settings available through the advertisement. The End User should review the advertiser or publisher’s privacy policy to understand how such entity will process any personal data entered by the End User or captured. If you would like Innovid to delete all records of your personal data, or exercise your rights of access, rectification, portability, or have any other questions or requests with respect to privacy, please send us an email at _[privacy@innovid.com.](mailto:privacy@innovid.com)_

Innovid works with Nielsen to better understand the reach of ad campaigns. To learn more about what information Nielsen collects, how it uses and shares that information and your choices, please visit _[http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy.](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy)_

Innovid collects personal data based on several bases, depending on the exact circumstances. Registration Data and Account Data is processed on the basis of a contract between Innovid and the customer; we are not able to provide services and meet the terms of our customer agreements without such processing. Personal data may also be processed on the basis of the legitimate interest Innovid has in serving and measuring advertising, and analyzing, improving, optimizing and personalizing its users’ experience.

To opt-out of any of the processing described in this policy, you may contact Innovid and its Data Protection Officer at privacy@innovid.com. Data subjects have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority (the UK ICO).  

#### Cross-Device Tracking

Innovid may, or may use the services of third party companies to, establish connections between a user’s devices and to provide interest-based advertising across devices. Cross-device connections allow Innovid to understand that a single user is accessing advertisements served or measured by Innovid from multiple devices and to synchronize or target advertising messages and/or measure the performance of advertisements across those devices. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices with respect to it, please: (1) visit the NAI Choices page located at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> to learn how to opt out of having your information collected in browsers for ad serving purposes; and (2) download the AppChoices application, available for iOS and Android (see <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices>), or visit the NAI’s Mobile Choices page located at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choice>, to learn how to opt out of having your information collected in mobile apps. Because web browsers and mobile apps have different identifiers, you will need to opt-out of each environment separately.  

#### Industry Self-Regulation 

Innovid is a member of the _[Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)_ (NAI) and adheres to the NAI Code of Conduct.  

#### Opt-Out of Interest-Based Advertising

##### Opt-out for Desktop or Mobile Web:

End Users can opt out of interest-based advertising served by Innovid on browsers used on desktop or mobile web.  to opt-out, or opt-out through the NAI page located [here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) In order to comply with an opt-out request, Innovid may set a non-unique cookie for the sole purpose of complying with such request. If an End User deletes its cookies or changes computers or devices after opting out, he or she will need to opt out again by clicking the link in this paragraph. Please note that where an End User blocks cookies on his or her browser, Innovid will be unable to set an opt-out cookie, and therefore unable to abide by such End User opt-out request.

##### Opt-out for Mobile Applications:

To opt-out of interest-based advertising for the mobile applications on your current device, the method of opting out depends on the type of device you have. Please also note that, in some cases (i.e., if you have an older device), it may be necessary for you to provide your device ID in order to opt out.

Opting out on Apple iOS devices: On iOS 6.0 you can select a setting that enables you to limit ad tracking. You can do this by clicking on Settings -> General -> About -> Advertising, and setting the Limit Ad Tracking function to ‘ON’. Alternatively, you can go to Settings -> Privacy -> Advertising and set the “Limit Ad Tracking” function to ‘ON’. On iOS 7.0, you can go to Settings -> Privacy -> Advertising and set the “Limit Ad Tracking” function to ‘ON’.

Opting out on Android devices: In Android devices with Google Play Services 4.0 and higher, You can opt out of interest-based advertising services by opening the Google Settings App, then clicking on Ads (under “Services”) and turning on the “Opt of interest-based ads” function.

Please also visit the NAI’s Mobile Choices Page located at <https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices#> for additional detailed instructions on how to use the advertising choice mechanisms for various devices.

##### Opt-out for CTV:

To opt-out of interest-based advertising for a CTV (i.e., televisions with third party connected applications, smart televisions and/or digital media streaming devices), please visit the NAI’s Internet Connected TV Opt-Out Instructions Page located at <https://www.networkadvertising.org/internet-connected-tv-choices/> for detailed instructions on how to use the advertising choice mechanisms for various types of CTVs.

Note: Following an opt-out using any of the above methods, Innovid’s system will still provide advertisements to the End User. Please note, however, that these advertisements may be less relevant to such End User’s interests.  

#### Data Retention

Personal data, whether from desktop, mobile devices, mobile applications, CTVs or other media may be retained for up to 12 months. Personal data may be anonymized and used for reporting and analysis, and may be stored as long as necessary to fulfill a legitimate business need or as required by law.  

#### Legal and Regulatory Compliance

Innovid reserves the right to disclose information if it believes, in good faith, that such disclosure is required to comply with legal or regulatory requirements, or to protect others’ rights or prevent harm, including in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.  

#### Third Party Service Providers

Innovid may retain certain third party service providers to perform functions and services on its behalf, such as cloud services for storing and processing information (e.g., Amazon Web Services and Akamai), customer relationship management services (e.g., Salesforce) and enterprise resource planning services (e.g., Priority). Innovid may share information with these third party service providers, but only to the extent necessary to perform such functions and services, and only pursuant to obligations on such third party service providers that are consistent with this Policy.

In all cases in which Innovid transfers any personal data to a third party, it will do so pursuant to a data protection agreement governing such transfers. Where personal data is transferred outside of the EU, appropriate safeguards are used such as E.U.- U.S. Privacy shield, see below.

#### Business Transfers

We may disclose personal data we have collected to third parties if we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets or if Innovid or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case information held by Innovid will be one of the transferred assets.  

#### Newsletter Subscriptions

You can change your subscription status with regards to Innovid’s email newsletters at any time. To unsubscribe, you can follow the instructions on the bottom of each newsletter, or by emailing _[support@innovid.com](mailto:support@innovid.com)_ and writing “Cancel Newsletter Subscription” in the subject line.  

#### Aggregate Information

Innovid may share aggregate and anonymous usage statistics regarding the Services with the public or businesses with whom Innovid works. Innovid may also use such aggregated information to help Innovid improve the design and delivery of its Services and increase its effectiveness for all users.  

#### Communication

Innovid may send to registered users, advertisers, agencies and publishers Services and/or account activity-related announcements from time to time.  

#### Data and Information Security

Innovid is committed to protect the security of the information it collects, and takes such measures as are in line with industry practice to safeguard the data in its possession from unauthorized alteration, destruction, access or misuse. We maintain tight controls over all the data we collect, retaining it in firewalled and secured databases with strictly limited and controlled access rights, to ensure it is secure. Access to personal data is protected and controlled by password and restricted permissions. Please note that where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password that enables you to access the Innovid Website or Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. Please be aware however that no method of Internet transmission or electronic storage is 100% secure. Innovid cannot ensure or warrant the absolute security of information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. For additional information regarding security, please contact: _[support@innovid.com](mailto:support@innovid.com)_  

#### Children’s Privacy

The Innovid Website and the Services are not intended for children under the age of 16, and children under the age of 16 are ineligible to register for an account on the Innovid Website. Innovid will never knowingly accept or solicit personal data from a visitor or End User under the age of 16, and will delete accounts that it believes to be in violation of this restriction. If you become aware that a child under the age of 16 has registered to use the Innovid Website or has provided Personally Identifiable Information to Innovid, please contact Innovid at _[privacy@innovid.com,](mailto:privacy@innovid.com)_ so that Innovid can confirm and take appropriate steps to remove such account and delete the information.  

#### International Data Transfers

The information that we collect from you and about you may be transferred to and stored in a country other than your country of residence, such as the USA, which may not offer the same level of protection of personal information as your country of residence. However, we will take contractual and/or other measures to ensure your personal data is protected. It may also be transferred to Israel, which has been recognized by the EU as having adequate data protection.

In addition to the above, Innovid Inc. adheres to the principles of the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield.  

#### EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield

Innovid Inc., a U.S. corporation, complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries, and the United Kingdom and Switzerland transferred to the United States pursuant to Privacy Shield.

Innovid, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to such data. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and data subject rights under the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

If you are from the European Union or Switzerland and would like to gain access to, or request amendment, correction or deletion of information that Innovid, Inc. holds about you, please contact us using the details in the “Contact Us” section below. We will consider and respond to your request in accordance with, as applicable, the EU-U.S. or Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield, and any applicable laws.

Innovid acknowledges the individual’s right to access their personal data and will provide you access to the personal information we hold about you to the extent it is reasonably available and allow you to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate information, as required and permitted by applicable law. If you’d like us to correct, amend, or delete any other personal information that you have provided to us, please send your request to us at [privacy@Innovid.com](mailto:privacy@mediamath.com) and we will respond to your request within 30 days.

You may request that we cease sending you any marketing communications (including by email and SMS) at any time by notifying us in writing using the contact details provided below or following any “unsubscribe” instructions included in any marketing communications which we send to you

We will also provide an individual opt-out or opt-in choice before we share your data with third parties other than our agents, or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized.  To request to limit the use and disclosure of your personal information, please submit a written request using the details in the “Contact Us” section below.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Innovid, Inc. is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

Under the Privacy Shield, Innovid, Inc. may remain liable if its third-party service providers process your personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles, unless we prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

EU or Swiss Individuals who believe that their personal information has not been processed in compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles may raise their complaint in the following ways:

  * In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Innovid, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information transferred to the United States pursuant to Privacy Shield. European Union and Swiss individuals with Privacy Shield inquiries or complaints should first contact Innovid, Inc. directly using the details in the “Contact Us” section below.  We will respond to your complaint within 45 days of receipt.
  * Innovid, Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers) for more information and to file a complaint. This service is provided free of charge to you.
  * If your Privacy Shield complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms.  See Privacy Shield Annex 1 at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>

Innovid, Inc. has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.

Pursuant to the Privacy Shield, Innovid, Inc. remains liable for the transfer of personal data to third parties acting as our agents unless we can prove we were not a party to the events giving rise to the damages.

#### Enforcement Complaints

Innovid has implemented processes to ensure compliance with this Policy and periodically verifies that the policy is accurate, comprehensive for the information intended to be covered, prominently displayed, completely implemented and accessible, and in conformity with the NAI Code of Conduct. We encourage interested persons to raise any concerns by emailing privacy@Innovid.com and we will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of information.

To address any issues regarding our compliance with the NAI Code of Conduct, Innovid, along with the NAI and other NAI members have created a compliance program that incorporates attestation reviews, a consumer complaint process, sanctions, and annual reporting to help ensure that member companies keep their promises to you and abide by the NAI Code of Conduct. Please refer to the NAI site for more information.  

### Contact Us

You may contact us and our Data Protection Officer at [privacy@innovid.com](mailto:privacy@innovid.com).

3-6 Kenrick Place  
Marylebone, W1U 6HD  
Tel: +44 203 813 2840  
In the US: see below.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Innovid reserves the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting the modified Privacy Policy on the Innovid Website. Your continued use of the Innovid Website or Services indicates your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.

**Our mailing address is:**

Innovid, Inc.  
Attn.: Privacy  
30 Irving Place, 12th Floor  
New York, NY 10003

Last updated: **November 15, 2019**
